fabrikbrands.com 2012-06-07

# Branding Agency | Digital Agency | Design Agency | Naming Agency | Fabrik Brands London

## Privacy Statement

If you have any questions or concerns about the information we hold about you, you can email us at [mail@fabrikbrands.com](mailto:mail@fabrikbrands.com)

### Security and privacy

Fabrik’s web site uses security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of any information under our control. We store the information in a database in a secure environment at our data/hosting centre.

We will not share, sell, or rent individual personal information without explicit permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you publications or emails based on your requests for information.

### Information tracked

At times we will use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. We may also track browser types to help us understand our visitors' needs related to our web site design.

There is an optional section of our web site where input forms require your name, postal address, email address and other information. These forms provide the ability to subscribe (opt-in) to receiving future emails from Fabrik. If you opt-in to receiving email communications from us, then we may send information to you about our other products or services.

Other information we collect via the Fabrik website may include:

  * Your preferences use of updates, recorded by emails we send (if you select to receive email updates on products and offers).
  * Your IP Address, this is a string of numbers unique to your computer that is recorded by our web server when you request any page or component on the website. This information is used to monitor your usage of fabrikbrands.com
  * Data recorded by the website which allows us to recognise you and your preferred settings, this saves you from re-entering information on return visits to the site. Such data is recorded locally on you computer through the use of cookies. Most browsers can be programmed to reject, or warn you before downloading cookies, information regarding this may be found in your browsers ‘help’ facility.

### Cookies

Client-side cookies are used to verify the login status of customers using products or services linked directly with our website. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site; however, the user may not be able to access all areas of our site.

### Links to other websites

Fabrik is not responsible for the content of any website linked from wwwfabrikbrands.com, and does not necessarily endorse the views expressed within them. Fabrik cannot guarantee that these links will work all of the time and has no control over the availability of any of these sites.

### Notification of changes

When there is a change to our privacy policy that may impact individual rights or the way we handle their information, Fabrik will notify those people who have provided opt-in (permission) to receive email or other communication from us, or who have consented to the collection of information. Any new policy will be posted on our site at least one week prior to taking effect. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.

### Your rights

You have the right to request a copy of any information that we currently hold about you. In order to receive such information please send your contact details including address and payment of £10 to cover administration expenses to the following address:

### Privacy Compliance

Fabrik Brands Limited  
98 Central Street  
London EC1V 8AJ

### Other websites

This privacy policy only covers this website. Any other websites which may be linked to by our website are subject to their own policy, which may differ from ours.
